https://www.pavepatch.com/privacy.php?osCsid=dq34rd4dl7kqiaqg3mdhop2660

Privacy Notice
PTI Pavement Repair Products Privacy Notice
We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We view protection of users privacy as a very important principle. We store and process your information on computers located in the United States that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. You can access and modify the information you provide us and choose not to receive certain communications by signing-in to your account. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles.
You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States. We may collect and store the following personal information: email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers: transactional information based on your activities on the Site (such as buying, shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item: correspondence through the Site, and correspondence sent to us: computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, and ad data: other information, including IP address and standard web log information: and supplemental information from third parties. (For example, if you incur a debt to PTI, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law. As another example, if the information you provide cannot be verified, we may ask you to send us additional information (such as your driver license, credit card statement, and/or a recent utility bill or other information confirming your address), or to answer additional questions online to help verify your information.
We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, or protect any persons rights, property, or safety. we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact the Store Owner
Continue
Categories
FASTPATCH DPR Concrete Repair
FASTPATCH DPR Asphalt Repair
FASTPATCH DPR Kits - Bulk
FASTPATCH ACR Kits
FASTPATCH 5000
FASTPATCH Cartridges
View All ProductsView Price List
Information FASTPATCH Product OverviewFASTPATCH Product Selection GuideEJC SEALANTS Product Selection GuideFastPatch DPR Installation GuideVideo How-To: FastPatch DPRVideo How-To: FastPatch MDVideo How-To: SlabGasketPhoto GalleriesArticles & NewsReferencesAbout UsF.A.Q. Shipping & Returns Privacy Notice Conditions of Use Contact Us Site Map
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Bestsellers SlabGasket Expansion Joint Replacement (Gray)SlabGasket XL Expansion Joint Replacement - 1 5/8" (2x4)SlabGasket Expansion Joint Replacement (Almond)SlabGasket XL Expansion Joint Replacement - 1 7/8"SlabGasket XL Expansion Joint Replacement - 2"
Shopping Cart 0 items
Specials FASTPATCH DPR Pourable Asphalt Repair 5-Gal Kit
FASTPATCH DPR Pourable A...$159.00$108.50 FASTPATCH DPR Pourable Asphalt Repair 5-Gal Kit - Pallet of (36)
FASTPATCH DPR Pourable A...$5,724.00$3,564.00 FASTPATCH DPR Concrete Repair 5-Gal Kit
FASTPATCH DPR Rapid Conc...$159.00$108.50 Eggbeater Style MixerPail Mixer / Mud Mixer
This...$15.99$12.95 FASTPATCH DPR Concrete Repair 5-Gal Kit, Pallet of (36)
FASTPATCH DPR Rapid Conc...$5,724.00$3,564.00 Manual 2:1 Dual Cartridge Gun 300mL x 150mLFor use with FASTPATCH EJC-NS,...$94.00$64.95 Manual 1:1 Dual Cartridge Gun 300mL x 300mLHand Operated Dual Cartridge G...$89.00$59.95 FASTPATCH EJC-50 Black 600mL (1-Pack)
FASTPATCH EJC-50 is a flexib...$57.50$44.95 FASTPATCH EJC-NS Gray 450mL (1-Pack)
FASTPATCH EJC-NS is a non-sa...$37.70$29.95 FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 350 600ml (1-Pack)FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 350 600ml ...$54.00$44.95
Reviews Great product. I used 1 5/8 inch to replace rotted 2x4s. Our ..
Newsletter Subscribe
Subscribe to our Newsletter
What's New FASTPATCH 100NS Sealant 20oz. Sausage Tube (1-Pack)FastPatch now offers a high pe...$45.50$37.95 FASTPATCH Asphalt Alligator Crack Repair Kit
FASTPATCH&t-rade; Asphalt...$169.00$129.00 FASTPATCH Asphalt Alligator Crack Repair Kit - Pallet of (32)
FASTPATCH&t-rade; Asphalt...$5,408.00$3,360.00 Pneumatic 1:1 Dispenser 300mL x 300mL AG-250Pneumatic 1:1 Polymer Dispense...$439.95 Pneumatic 2:1 Dispenser 300mL x 150mL AG-251Pneumatic 2:1 Polymer Dispense...$399.95 FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 600ml (12-Pack)FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 600ml (12-...$399.00$359.00 (FREE Shipping)FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 600ml (1-Pack)FASTPATCH POLYPRIME 600ml (1-P...$39.90$34.95 FASTPATCH 5000 Concrete Repair 5-Gal Kit, Pallet of (36)
FASTPATCH 5000
Rapid Co...$6,084.00$3,744.00 Manual 20oz. Sausage Pack Dispenser GunManual Single Cartridge 20oz. ...$59.00$49.95 CEG-20 Electric 20oz. Sausage Pack Dispenser GunCEG-20 Electric 20oz. Sausage ...$369.95$319.95 (FREE Shipping)
Currencies
U.S. DollarEuro
Manufacturers Please SelectKraft Tool Co.POLYQuikSlabGasketWell Made Tools
We Accept
